Starrika McCloud

Full Stack Developer

Front-End / Back-End Development

Cybre3@gmail.com □

(609) 815 1154

Bessemer, AL ?

linkedin.com/in/starrika-mccloud-802a251a1

starrika-mccloud-portfolio.herokuapp.com

github.com/Cybre3

Full Stack Developer with 10 years of Entertainment Technology experience.

Troubleshooting, material digest and organizational strengths allow me to assess and resolve, hindering, daily issues. Resolutions include but are not limited to: Scaling organizational networks, advising technicians in problem solving and refactoring equipment behavior programs.

Clients and fellow technicians have expressed significant increase in efficiency.

Achievements/Awards

NCL: Company Excellence - "Vacation Hero" and "Outstanding Team" awards, with Norwegian Cruise Line.

Freelance: "Best Lighting Design" nomination by NJACT Perry Awards.

Non-profit: Founder of non-profit organization, "Storehouse Strength."

Education

Kingsland University – Oct. 2020 – Oct. 2021 Certified Full Stack Development

Mercer County Community College – Aug. 2011 – Dec. 2015 Entertainment Technology

Mercer County Community College – Aug. 2009 – May 2011 Electronic Engineering Technology

Skills

Git | GitHub HTML | CSS JavaScript PHP

PHP NoSQL

Test Driven Development (TDD)
MongoDB | Express | React | Node.js
REST Services | Postman
Jest | Mocha | Chai
Netlify | Heroku

Troubleshooting
Adaptability
Organization
Detail Oriented
Teamwork
Research
Composed
Communication

Currently Learning

Java Angular

Experience

Oct. 2020 – Current Full Stack Developer • Projects

- Product Sorter / Item List Sorter
- Forecaster Uses third party API to display forecast at a given location
- Word Manifest Takes in amount of words and gives a word count and count of same words in a unique layout.
- Fisher Catches Keeps track of your fishing catches by entry
- Course Enroll site, Wiki Blog, Rubik's Cube webpage

Upcoming projects: Mortal Kombat App, Entertainment Tech App and E-commerce Lip gloss website.

2013 – December 2021

Lighting Technician and Designer • Freelance • Owner MTS

- Scale organizational network by installing repeaters and extended data points for efficiency and effectiveness.
- Collaborate with directors and creative team.
- Maintain / repair equipment Update virtual Rep plots.
- Troubleshoot electrical circuits, signal connection, Lighting software and intelligent lighting fixtures.
- Design, program and keep lights for shows/events/musicals.

Note: Other work experiences, not relevant to field, exist but not included.